-What's the matter?
-Someone on the subway licked my neck!
- 왜 그래?
- 전철에서 누가 내 목을 핥았어!
Willy's still alive!
윌리가 아직 살아있구나!
-What are you doing?
-My mom called.
- 너희 뭐해?
- 엄마가 전화했어
They're announcing
our engagement in the paper.
신문에 우리 약혼 소식을 싣겠대
-We're looking for a good picture.
-I'm afraid that does not exist.
- 우리가 잘 나온 사진 찾는 거야
- 안됐지만 그런 건 없어
There are great pictures of us.
아냐, 잘 나온 것 많아
No, there are great pictures of you
next to a guy who's going like this...
넌 잘 나와도 네 옆의 난
이러고 있는 사진이지
Oh, my God, that's the creep that
you're with at the Statue of Liberty.
자유의 여신상 앞에
너랑 서있는 그 괴짜구나!
I don't know what it is.
I just can't take a good picture.
도무지 모르겠어
절대로 사진이 안 받아
Here's a great one.
이거 좋다
-Yeah, I'm not in that.
-No, but look at me, all tan.
- 난 안 나왔잖아
- 하지만, 썬탠한 내 모습 좀 봐
Why don't you get portraits done
by a professional photographer?
너희들 전문 사진가한테 가서
사진을 찍는 게 어때?
That's a great idea. I bet they have
one of those wind machines.
좋은 생각이다
아마 바람 장치도 있겠지
Yeah, that's great. Next to that,
Chandler won't look so stupid.
그거 좋다, 그러고 있으면
챈들러가 덜 바보같아 보일 걸
-Chandler, what do you say?
-All right, but I'm not going.
- 챈들러, 어때?
- 그래, 근데, 이런 내가 아니라
"I'm" going.
이런 내가 간다는 걸 알아둬
The One With The Engagement Picture
Dude, that reverse lay-up.
그 리버스 레이업
대단했지?
-And how about those three-pointers?
-Amazing.
- 3점슛들은 어떻고?
- 굉장했어
And those guys were this close
to letting us play this time too.
그 놈들 이번엔 거의 우리도
같이 하게 해줄 뻔 했지
Hey, look. Phoebe's talking
to Cute Coffeehouse Guy.
저기 봐, 피비가
'잘생긴 카페 남자'랑 얘기한다
You call him "Cute Coffeehouse Guy"?
We call him "Hums While He Pees."
'잘생긴 카페 남자'라고 부르냐?
우린 '콧노래하며 쉬하며'라고 하지
Yes, and we call Ross
"Lingers in the Bathroom."
그리고 로스를
'화장실에서 머무는 자'라고 하지
Hey, you guys, "Hums While He Pees"
just asked me out.
'콧노래하며 쉬하며'가
방금 데이트 신청했다!
-I thought that guy was married.
-He's getting divorced.
- 유부남인줄 알았는데
- 그런데, 곧 이혼한대
Ross, maybe you know him.
로스, 너 그 사람
알지도 모르겠다
It's not a club.
이건 클럽이 아니야
If he's getting a divorce,
is it a good idea to date him?
이혼남이라면, 그 사람과
사귀는 게 현명할까?
-Hey, divorced men are not bad men.
-That's on the napkins at the club.
- 이혼했다고 나쁜 남자는 아냐
- 라고 클럽의 냅킨에 쓰여있지
-I gotta go to work.
-You don't have to go for a half-hour.
- 사무실에 돌아가야겠다
- 아직 30분 있잖아
My assistant, Tag, does sit-ups
in the office during lunch.
내 조수가 점심 때 사무실에서
윗몸 일으키기 하거든
I could just spread him on a cracker.
걔를 그냥 크래커에다
발라먹고 싶어
Rach, why would you hire this guy?
걔가 좋으면 왜 고용했어?
-You know you can't date him, right?
-I know that.
- 사귀면 안 되는 건 알지?
- 그럼, 알지
We spend so much time together,
he should call me his "work-wife."
근데, 우린 농담했어
같이 시간을 많이 보내니까
날 '직장 아내'라고
불러야겠대
곧 '자기가 알던 그
해고당한 여자'라고 부르겠다
Soon he'll be able to call you "that
lady he knew that got fired."
I won't get fired, because
I'm not gonna act on it.
해고 안 당해
그런 행동 안 할 테니까
You wouldn't mind
if he was dating someone?
딴 사람이랑 만나도
신경 안 쓰겠네, 그럼?
Why, is he? He is, isn't he?
He's dating that slut in marketing.
왜, 누구 만난대? 그렇지?
그 마케팅부 걸레랑 사귀지?
Maybe I should open
a divorced men's club.
역시 이혼남 클럽을
하나 열까봐
Dude, that's so sad.
그거 너무 비참하다
I could put a basketball court
in the back.
뒷마당에다 농구 코트도
지을 수 있겠지
Could I play?
나도 써도 돼?
Oh, no sit-ups today, Tag?
오늘은 윗몸 일으키기 안해요
태그?
-I just did them.
-Well, drop and give me 10 more.
- 방금 했어요
- 그럼, 지금 10개 더해
What?
네?
I had a drink with lunch.
나 점심 때 한 잔 했거든
- 가격 보고서는 들어왔어요?
- 어젯밤 작성했어요
-Did those cost reports come in?
-I did them last night.
4장만 복사해 줄래요?
Could you make me 4 copies?
- 그럼요
- 고마워요
-Sure.
-Great, thank you.
- 안녕
- 안녕, 무슨 일이죠?
-Hey, Rachel.
-Hi, Melissa. What's up?
지금 상점에 뭐 사러
나가려던 참이었는데
I'm just about to go out to the store.
배낭에 뭣 좀 넣으려고
Get some stuff to put in my backpack.
건과, 그라놀라 시리얼, 그런 거
Dried fruit and granola,
and stuff like that.
- 무슨 일인데요?
- 태그 있어요?
-What's up?
-Is Tag here?
아니, 왜?
No. Why?
오늘 저녁일로
얘기 좀 할까 해서요
I was gonna talk to him about tonight.
정말? 태그한테
마음이 있는가보지?
Really? You got a little crush
on Tag there, do ya?
서로 눈길을
좀 보내긴 했죠
We've been flirting back and forth...
근데, 오늘밤엔 좀 더
진전을 볼 수 있을까 해서
but I was hoping tonight it would
turn into something a little more.
멜리사, 심하다
여긴 남자 탈의실이 아니죠?
Easy there, Melissa.
This ain't a locker room, okay.
근데, 오늘밤 무슨
계획이 있다고 한 것 같던데
But you know, I remember him saying
that he had plans tonight.
- 오, 저런
- 오, 그래요
-Oh, no.
-Oh, yeah.
자, 다시 일자리로
All right, back to work.
저기, 그거
태그 배낭 아니예요?
Hey, isn't that Tag's backpack?
난 회사의 고약한 년으로 찍히기
싫지만, 그 쪽 상관한테 말한다
I don't want to be known as the office
bitch, but I'll call your supervisor.
좋아요, 모니카, 아주 좋아요
Great, that's great, Monica. Great.
챈들러, 한 번 웃어줄래요?
Now, Chandler, you want to
give us a smile?
좋아요
Okay.
-I'm sorry, is the seat uncomfortable?
-No, I am.
- 미안하지만, 자리가 불편해요?
- 아뇨, 불편한 건 나죠
Chandler, I know you can do this.
You have a beautiful smile.
챈들러, 넌 할 수 있어
네 미소는 아름다워
-I do?
-Yeah.
- 정말?
- 그래
Maybe you don't have to smile.
Let's try something else.
웃지 않는 건 어떨까?
다른 걸 시도해보자
- 섹시한 표정 해 봐
- 그럴께
-Try looking sexy.
-Okay.
하지 말든가
Or not.
안녕, 조이, 여긴 웬일이야?
Hi, Joey, what are you doing here?
근처에 오디션이 있는데
셔츠에다 소스를 흘렸어
I got an audition down the street,
and I spilled sauce on my shirt.
- 남는 셔츠 있니?
- 그래, 물론
-You got an extra one?
-Yeah, sure.
여기
Here.
잘됐다
Great.
랄프 로렌 아닌 건 없니?
You got anything that's
not Ralph Lauren?
글쎄, 없겠지?
Yeah, I don't think so, Joe.
이거면 되겠다
I guess this'll be fine.
- 너 오늘 저녁 뭐하니?
- 아무것도, 왜?
-What are you doing tonight?
-Nothing. Why?
내 조수를 데리고 나가줄래?
내가 돈 낼께
How would you feel about
taking out Tag? I'll pay.
남자랑 데이트 하라는 거면
돈이 많이 들텐데
It's gonna take a lot of money for
me to go out on a date with a dude.
데이트를 하라는 게 아냐
I'm not asking you to go on
a date with him.
정말?
돈이 좀 필요하긴 한데
Really? Because I could kind of
use the money.
이사온 지 얼마 안 됐고
남자 친구들도 없어
He's new in town and
he doesn't have any guy friends.
야구장에라도 데려가든지 해
고맙게 여길께
Take him to a ball game or something.
I'd appreciate it.
- 문제 없어
- 고마워
-Yeah, okay, no problem.
-Thank you.
야, 도너츠잖아!
Ooh, hey, doughnuts!
알겠다, 이렇게 해보자
I know. Let's try a look...
멀리 바라보는
경이로운 표정
of far-off wonderment.
우리의 미래를 바라보며
결혼과 다가올 날들을 생각하자
Gaze into our future and think about
our marriage and the days to come.
챈들러, 얼굴이 왜 그래?
Chandler, what is the matter
with your face?
이 사진 제목은
'겔러양과 빙군 약혼'이야
This picture should say
"Geller and Bing to be married"...
'동네 아줌마, 물에 빠진
저능아 구하다'가 아냐
not "Local woman saves
drowning moron."
이봐요, 웃지 마요, 얜
내 '물에 빠진 저능아'라구요
Hey, don't laugh at him.
He's my drowning moron.
그래, 그 표정!
찍어요, 찍어!
That's it, that's it!
Take it, take it!
'센트럴 퍼크'
이거 좋은데
I like this one.
'사랑해, 그래서 널 죽여야 해'
라고 하는 것 같다
It seems to say, "I love you and
that's why I have to kill you."
다 나쁠 리 있나?
Can't all be bad.
섹시한 눈을 하고 있는 거
찾아봐
Find the one where you make
your bedroom eyes.
거기 있다
There it is.
세상에,
그게 내 섹시한 눈이야?
Oh, my God,
those are my bedroom eyes?
도대체 나랑 왜 잤니?
Why did you ever sleep with me?
지금 정말로
그 얘길 하고 싶니?
Do you really want to pull
at that thread?
- 정말 재미있었어요
- 나도요
-I'm having a good time.
-Me too.
전철에서 그 사람이
목을 핥아서 안됐네요
Sorry that guy on the subway
licked your neck.
괜찮아요
내 친구예요
No, that's okay. He's a friend.
뻔뻔스럽지만
I don't mean to be presumptuous...
내일 있는 볼룸 댄스
결승전 표가 있거든요
but I have tickets to the
ballroom-dancing finals tomorrow.
그래요, 난
Yeah, I..
준결승전을 놓쳐서
뭐가 뭔지 모를 것 같은데
Well, I missed the semifinals,
so I think I would just be lost.
싱겁지만, 상사한테서
이 표를 받았...
I know it's lame, but I got
these tickets from my boss..
세상에, 안 돼, 안 돼!
Oh, no, no, no, my God!
알았어요
흥분하지 말아요, 갈께요
Okay, don't freak out. I'll go.
내 전아내, 휘트니예요
It's my ex-wife, Whitney.
저 여자 상대할 수 없어요
미쳤거든요
I cannot deal with her now.
She's crazy.
알겠어요, 잠깐만
Okay, I know. Hold on.
- 로스
- 응?
-Hey, Ross.
-Yeah.
저기 밖에 휘트니거든
카일의 전부인이야
That's Whitney, Kyle's ex-wife
out there.
우리 빠져나갈 동안 저 여자
주의를 돌려줄 수 있니?
Do you think you could divert her
so we could slip out?
뭐? 못 해
What? No.
좋아, 근데, 볼룸 댄스
결승전 표가 두 장 있어
Okay, but I have two tickets to
the ballroom-dance finals.
난 못해, 피비
I don't think so, Phoebe.
알았어, 할께
All right, I'll do it.
- 단지 친구니까 해준다
- 그래
-But just because you're a friend.
-Okay.
안녕, 진저 로저스
Hi, Ginger.
내 열쇠 돌려줘
I want my key back.
- 없어
- 거기 있잖아
-I don't have it.
-It's right there.
알았다, 셜록 홈즈
Okay, Sherlock.
미안하지만
너 가줘야겠다
I'm sorry, but you'd better go.
그냥 카일 전부인 일로
고맙다는 말을 하고 싶었어
I just wanted to thank you
for diverting Kyle's ex.
천만에
나중에 얘기하자
You're welcome.
We'll talk about it later.
- 안녕, 휘트니
- 안녕, 로스
-Hi, Whitney.
-Hi, Ross.
- 아침 먹으러 갈까요?
- 그래요
-Are you ready for breakfast?
-Yep.
카일 전부인?
주의를 돌리랬지, 데이트하랬니?
Kyle's ex-wife? You were supposed
to divert her, not date her.
잠깐 기다려줄래요?
이 여자랑 얘기 할 동안
Can you give me a second
while I talk to this woman...
이 여자, 여기서
자지 않았어요
who, by the way, did not
spend the night?
Sure.
- 그래요
난 주의를 돌렸어, 같이
좋은 시간을 보냈다구, 알아?
I did divert her, and we ended up
having a great time, okay?
볼룸 댄스 구경했어?
Watching ballroom dancing?
그래, 거기서 우린 둘 다
멋지다는 걸 알았지
Yes, that's where we realized
we were both super cool people.
카일이 저 여자에 대해
나쁜 얘기를 해줬어
Look, Kyle just told me
some really bad stuff about her.
- 어떤 얘기?
- 아주 못됐대
Like what?
Like she's really mean, and
she's overly critical and..
너무 비판적이고
물어보지도 않고 방을
아주 밝은 색으로 칠한대
She will paint a room a really bright
color without even checking with you.
알았어
Okay.
그리고, 섹스를 무기로 삼는대
And she uses sex as a weapon.
경고 고마워
Thank you for warning me.
아침 먹을 때 방 페인트칠과
섹스 무기를 조심할께
At breakfast, I'll be on alert for
room painting and sex weapons.
- 그래도 만날 거야?
- 그래
-You're still gonna go out with her?
-Yeah.
내가 방금 한 말
못 들었어?
Well, didn't you hear
what I just said?
피비, 정보 출처를 생각해 봐
Phoebe, come on.
I mean, consider the source.
전남편이니 당연히 그렇게 말하지
그럼, 실례
Of course her ex-husband's gonna say
that stuff. Now if you'll excuse me.
들어봐, 저 여자 미쳤어!
Listen to me, she is crazy!
저, 이 문 방음이 아닌데요
Your door isn't soundproof.
봐, 저 여잔 맘에 차는 게 없어
You see? Nothing is good enough
for her.
- 안녕하세요
- 안녕, 태그
-Morning.
-Hi, Tag.
- 어젯밤 조이랑 즐거웠어요?
- 네, 농구 보러 갔어요
-Did you have fun with Joey?
-Yeah, we went to the Knicks game.
잘됐네요
That's nice.
그리고 바에 갔는데, 조이가
여자들 소개시켜 줬어요
Then we went to a bar, and he
hooked us up with all these women.
여자들?
늙은 여자들 말이예요?
Women? You mean, like old women?
좀 늙었죠, 30살 정도
Kind of old, like 30.
전에는 바에서
여자하고 말 못 했는데
I never used to be able
to talk to girls in bars...
어젯밤엔 전화번호를
20개는 받았죠
but I got like 20 phone numbers
last night.
그거 잘됐네
That's great.
조이가 몇가지
가르쳐줬나 봐요?
Joey must have really taught
you some stuff.
조금요
A little.
잘 지내요?
How you doing?
봐, 멋진 미소잖아?
편하고 자연스럽고
See? That's a great smile.
Easy, natural.
이제 카메라가 있다 생각해
Now pretend I have a camera.
- 표정 바꾸고 있잖아
- 어쩔 수 없어
-You're changing it.
-I can't help it.
난 배우 이력서 사진 찍을 때
어떻게 하는지 알아?
You want to know what I do
when I take resume shots?
나한테 돈을 꾸지
Borrow money from me?
Yeah. Okay, first of all,
you want to make it look spontaneous.
그래, 좋아, 일단
자연스럽게 보여야 돼
So here's what I do. I look down,
look down, keep looking down.
그래서 난 이렇게, 밑을 내려봐
내려봐, 계속 내려다봐
그리고서, 올려다봐
Then I look up.
봤지? 네가 해봐
See? Now you try.
내려다봐, 내려다봐
계속 내려다봐
Look down. You're looking down.
Keep looking down.
너 신발에 왜 잼이 묻었냐?
Why is there jelly on your shoe?
도너츠를 먹었거든
I had a donut.
너 어젯밤 태그랑
재미 봤다면서
So, I heard you had some fun
with Tag last night.
그래, 걔 괜찮더라
Yeah, he's all right.
걔한테 '조이'같이 되는 법
가르치느라 재밌었지
Yeah, and you had fun teaching him
how to be all "Joey."
- 뭐라고?
- 그 여자들 말야
-What?
-You know, all the women.
여자 다루는 법은
가르칠 수가 없어
You can't teach someone
to be good with women.
챈들러랑은 실패한
이유가 바로 그거지
That's why I never had
any luck with Chandler.
나 바로 여기 있다
I'm right here.
다시는 걔랑 같이
다니지 말아줄래?
Would you mind just not
going out with him again?
너랑 걔랑 그 많은
여자들을 생각하면...
Just the idea of you and he
and all these women..
내 조수이고
사귀면 안 되는 것 알아!
I know he's my assistant,
and we can't date!
하지만 신경 거슬려, 응?
But it bothers me, all right?
안 돼, 나한테서 걔를
빼앗아갈 순 없어
No, no, no, you can't take him
away from me.
난 드디어 헌팅하는데
최상의 파트너를 구했다고!
I got a great partner to pick
up girls with. Finally!
나 아직도 여기 있어
I'm still right here.
적어도 걔한테 말은 해줘
Will you talk to him...
많은 여자랑 만나는 게
얼마나 공허하고 보람없는 지를
and tell him how unsatisfying
this dating-tons-of-women thing is?
뭐라고?
What?
내 맘이 진정될 때까지만
그가 아무도 안 만났으면 해서 그래
I don't want him to meet anybody
until I'm over my crush.
꼭 진정될 거고
I will get over it.
사랑하는 건 아니니까
그냥 육체적인 도취야
It's not like I love him.
It's just physical.
난 항상 이러거든
널 처음 봤을 때도 그랬어
I get these crushes all the time.
I had a crush on you at first.
알아, 모니카가 얘기했어
I know. Monica told me.
날 처음 봤을 때도?
Did you have a crush on me
when we first met?
응, 물론
Yeah, sure.
너흰 내가 안 보이냐?
Can you people not see me?
그래, 얘기해줄 거야?
Will you talk to him?
- 글쎄, 레이첼
- 랄프 로렌 셔츠 10장 줄께
-I don't know, Rach.
-I'll give you 10 Ralph Lauren shirts.
한 장
One.
아니 10장, 10장이랬어
취소 없기
No, 10. You said 10.
You can't take that back.
나랑 얘기하자고요?
You wanted to talk to me?
글쎄
나 줄 것 뭐 없니?
I don't know.
You got something for me?
레이첼이 이거 전하래요
Yeah, this is from Rachel.
10장, 그래
Ten. Okay.
태그,
여자가 너무 많아도 문제란다
Tag, there's such a thing
as too many women.
- 정말요?
- 너의 경우 말이지
-Really?
-Yeah, for you.
- 자기 이제 오네
- 자기 이제 왔지
-Hey, there you are.
-There I am.
- 괜찮아?
- 조이가 긴장을 풀어준다고
-You okay?
-Yeah, Joey said I needed to relax.
항히스타민제를 먹였어
So he gave me an antihistamine.
뭐라고?
What?
전철에서 잠들어서
브루클린까지 갔다
I fell asleep on the subway
and went to Brooklyn.
브루클린은 멀더라
Brooklyn is far.
제 정신이야?
What were you thinking?
걱정 마, 왜냐?
이제 사진 찍을 줄 알거든
But don't worry, because
I know how to take a picture now.
이거 봐라, 밑을 봐
Okay, see. Look down.
밑을 봐
Look down.
- 챈들러?
- 응?
-Chandler?
-Yeah?
- 안녕
미친 여자는 어때?
네 토끼 아직 안 끓여먹었니?
How are things going with Crazy?
Has she cooked your rabbit yet?
넌 한 쪽 얘기만 듣고 있는 거야
알았어?
Listen, you are hearing one side
of the story. Okay?
참고로, 카일한테 페인트 샘플을
30개도 더 보여줬대
FYI, she must have shown Kyle
over 30 paint samples...
방을 칠하기 전에 말야
before she painted that room.
대답은 항상 이랬대
'난 쥐똥만큼도 관심 없어'
And his response to each one was,
"I don't give a tiny rat's ass."
그 여자, 인테리어에
시간을 덜 쓰고
Maybe she should have spent
a little less time decorating...
침실에 시간을
더 썼으면 좋았을 걸
and a little more time
in the bedroom.
우린 그런 문제는 없을 걸
I don't think we are going
to have that problem...
난 그 사람처럼 감정이
무디지 않아서일지도
but maybe it's because I am not
emotionally unavailable.
그가 감정이 무디다고?
You think he's
emotionally unavailable?
그럴 수도 있겠지
I think he can be.
아마 그 여자가
Maybe he wouldn't be...
밤마다 집에서 일만 하지
않았다면 또 모르지
if she didn't bring the office
home every night.
여자가 인생 목표가
있는 게 뭐 죄야?
Excuse her for knowing
what she wants to do with her life.
1997년, 새해 전날 밤엔
목표가 아주 뚜렷했지
Well, she certainly knew what
she was doing New Year's Eve 1997.
네가 그걸 물고
넘어질 줄 알았어!
I knew you were going
to throw that in my face!
3년전 일이야
사과하고 또 사과했다구
That was three years ago.
She apologized and apologized.
더 이상 뭘 원해?
What more do you want?!
우린 지난 6년을
돌려받길 원해!
We want the last 6 years back!
우리도 그래! 우리도!
So do we! So do we!
그런 꼴을 보게해서 미안해요
I'm sorry you had to see that.
- 안녕하세요, 레이첼
- 안녕
-Morning, Rachel.
-Hi.
그래서, 어젯밤엔 뭐했어요?
Hey, so, what'd you do last night?
- 조이랑 나갔어요
- 그래?
-Went out with Joey.
-Yeah?
또 아가씨들 쫓아다니며
밤을 샜어요?
Another night of bird-dogging
the chicas?
아뇨, 좋은 대화를 가졌어요
No, we had a really good talk.
더 이상
바 같은 데 안 갈까봐요
I don't think I'll do
the bar scene anymore.
와, 예상치 못했는데
Wow, I did not see that coming.
사실, 저하고 안맞아요
It's just not really who I am.
언제나 더 행복했던 때가...
왜 부장님께 이런 얘길 하죠?
I've always been happier when..
Why am I telling you this?
- 관심도 없으실 텐데
- 아니, 관심있어
-You don't care about this stuff.
-Yes, I do.
'언제나 더 행복했던 때가...'
라고 했지?
You were saying,
"I'm happier when I..."
한 사람하고만 사귈 때죠
When I'm in a relationship.
- 여자 친구가 있는 게 좋아요
- 그래요?
-I love having a girlfriend.
-Really?
호강시켜 줄 사람
Someone I can spoil, you know.
호강?
Spoil?
한 가지 물어볼께요
Let me ask you something.
천생연분이라는 게
있다고 생각하세요?
Do you believe there's one perfect
person for everyone?
생각이 들기 시작하네
I'm starting to.
그런 사람이 있다면
뭔가 행동을 해야겠죠?
If that person's in your life
you should do something?
물론이죠, 네
Yes. Hell, yes.
좋아요, 다 해결됐어요
All right, then, it's settled.
- 옛여자 친구를 다시 만나겠어요
- 나도 좋아!
-I'm getting back together with my ex.
-I would love to!
네?
What?
여보세요?
Hello?
이거 시간 좀 걸리겠어
잠깐 실례
This is gonna be a while. Excuse me.
그래요
Yeah.
맙소사!
My God!
미안, 신경 거슬려?
Oh, I'm sorry. Is that annoying?
침실에서 이기적이란 말이
나온 김에, 휘트니는 어때?
And speaking of being selfish in bed,
how's Whitney?
침실에서의 이기적인 행동은
Maybe she wouldn't have to be
selfish in bed...
그가 뭐가 어디에 있는 줄
알았다면 필요없겠지
if someone else knew where
everything was.
오, 그 사람은 알아
Oh, he knows.
대부분은
For the most part.
잘 됐다, 둘 다 여기 있군
Oh, hey.
Good, you're both here.
얘기 좀 해야겠어요
We kind of need to talk.
- 둘이 같이?
- 웬일이죠?
-Both of you together?
-What's up?
어젯밤 몇가지 물건 가지러
카일네에 들렀는데
Well, I went over to Kyle's last night
to pick up a few things...
둘이 회상하기 시작했어요
and we got to reminiscing.
밤새도록 얘기했는데
We talked most of the night...
서로한테 화가 났던 건 바로
and realized the reason
we're angry with each other...
아직 서로에 대한 감정이
있어서란 걸 깨달았죠
is because there are still
feelings there.
그래서...
So...
그냥 말해요, 카일!
Oh, just say it, Kyle!
다시 시도해 보려고요
We're gonna try again.
맨날 칭얼대고 계속
주의를 요구한다면서요?
What about her whining,
and her constant need for attention?
고치도록 할 거예요
I'll work on that.
물론이지, 당신은
너무나 쉽게 변하니까
Right, because you're so
capable of change.
쉬하면서 콧노래하는 건 알아요?
You know, he hums when he pees.
- 알지요
- 변기 못 맞추는 건 아나
-I do know.
-Makes him miss the bowl, but whatever.
너무 미안해요
We're so sorry.
괜찮아요, 우린 당신들 필요없어
난 이미 잊었어
That's all right. We don't need you.
I'm over it already.
난 이제 쥐똥만큼도 상관 안해
Yeah, and I don't even give
a tiny rat's ass.
그래요, 갈께요
Yeah, we're gonna go.
미안해
I'm sorry.
피비, 저 여자,
네 말이 맞았어
Phoebe, you were right about her.
정말 섹스를
무기로 삼으려 했다
You know, she did try to use
sex as a weapon.
등을 좀 다쳤어
Yeah, I hurt my back a little.
저 작자, 다른 짓 할 때도
콧노래 한다
You know, he hums while he does
other stuff too.
저 둘 없는 게 훨씬 낫다
We're better off without them.
둘이 또 깨져도 네 그
'비참한 남자 클럽'에 들이지 마
Even if they break up again, you better
not let him in your sad men's club.
- 이혼남 클럽이야
- 그게 그거지 뭐
-Divorced men's club.
-Po-tay-to, po-tah-to.
얘들아, 이거 봐
Hey, check it out.
- 우리 엄마가 신문 보냈어
- 보자
-My mom sent me the paper.
-Let's see it.
- 그래, 잘 나왔다
- 아주 잘 어울리는 한쌍인데
-Oh, yeah, that looks good.
-You make a very attractive couple.
- 우리 둘 좋아보인다
- 정말
-Yeah, we look great together.
-We really do.
알았어
Okay.
우리 둘의 애는
어떨까 상상해봐
Imagine what our kids would look like.
상상 안해도 되는데
We don't have to imagine.
나랑 결혼한다구
I'm marrying her.
어디 두고 보지
We'll just see.